let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:" The public files in a class library usually contain",
		answer:" Class declarations",
		options:[
			" Class declarations",
			"Variable definition",
			"Constant definitions",
			"Member function definitions"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"Turbo C++ library function can be used",
		answer:"All of these",
		options:[
			"Draw lines and circles",
			"Write text in a variety of fonts and sizes",
			"Color any closed figure",
			"All of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"Keyword typed is used to declare",
		answer:"A synonym for an existing type",
		options:[
			"A synonym for an existing type",
			"Absence of a type",
			" Objects that can be modified outside of a program control",
			"A member function that is defined in a subclass"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"When a language has the capability to produce new data types, it is called",
		answer:"  None of these",
		options:[
			"Extensible",
			"Encapsulated",
			"Reprehensible",
			" None of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"In a class specified, data or functions and designated private are accessible",
		answer:"To member functions of that class",
		options:[
			"Only to public members of class",
			"Only if you know the password",
			"To any function in the program",
			"To member functions of that class"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"Which of the following are good reasons to use an object oriented language?",
		answer:"We can define our own data types",
		options:[
			"We can define our own data types",
			"Program statements are simpler than in procedural language",
			" We can define our own data types",
			"None of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"___  type is further divided into int and char.",
		answer:"Integral",
		options:[
			"Float",
			"Char",
			"Int",
			"Integral"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"___ data type to indicate the function does not return a value.",
		answer:" Public",
		options:[
			" Public",
			" Void",
			"Main",
			" Void"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"Which operator requires one operand?",
		answer:"Unary",
		options:[
			"Unary",
			"Binary",
			"Ternary",
			"Both (a) and (b)"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Which one gives special meaning to the language compiler?",
		answer:"Keywords",
		options:[
			"Constant",
			"Keywords",
			" Variable",
			"Compiler"
		]
	},
];